很安静 对吧
- Wow. - Quiet, right?
是的
Yeah.
我跟你说 那是双层玻璃
I mean, that's double-paned glass right there.
你在这里被杀了都没人会知道
You could get murdered in here, and no one would know.
丽塔的那张桌子放这吗
Ooh. What about Rita's desk over here?
丽塔 不 你疯了吗
Rita? No, are you crazy?
我可不想把这景色浪费在丽塔身上
I'm not wasting that view on Rita.
那是你的位置
That's your spot.
不 我要有自己的办公室和蒂娜
Hell, no, I'm getting my own office and my own Tina.
他的名字将是西奥多
His name will be Theodore.
想象一下
Just imagine sitting here
菲利普·莫里斯和西格拉姆坐在一起
with Philip Morris and Seagram's over here,
就为了把他们的钱
and they're just tripping over themselves
都给我们
to give us all their dough.
对不起 赫夫纳先生 他在开会
"Sorry, Mr. Hefner. He's in a meeting.
当然 你可以借用飞机
"But sure, you can borrow the jet.
一定要把油箱加满
Just make sure you top off the tank..."
-嘿  -因为上次
- Hey! - "Because last time--"
这是施工区 谁让你进来的
This is an active work zone. Who let you in?
迈克尔·施瓦兹
Michael Schwartz.
在我揍你之前给你十秒钟滚开
You got ten seconds before I kick your ass.
快快快快快 好了 我们走了 我们走了
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Okay, we're going, we're going!
安全帽留下
Leave the hard hats.
你知道你的爱
♪ You know that your love ♪
就像一把小提琴
♪ Is like a violin ♪
宝贝 当你吻我的时候
♪ Baby, when you kiss me ♪
你知道音乐就开始了
♪ You know the music begins ♪
嗨 打扰一下 警官
Hi. Excuse me, Officer.
你好 有什么问题吗
Hi, is there a problem here?
小姐 你是底袋钱公司的员工吗
Are you an employee of Bottom Dollar, Miss?
理论上来讲 是的
Technically, yes.
但实际上 我认为自已更像是一个有创造力的领导者
But I think of myself more as a creative leader, actually.
我刚完成我的新杂志的首刊
I just finished the maiden issue of my new magazine.
恭喜
Congratulations.
-谢谢  -嘿 肯尼
- Thank you. - Hey, Kenny.
帮这位女士减轻一下负担
Help lighten this nice lady's load.
什么
What?
哦 不 我很抱歉
Oh, oh, no, I'm so sorry.
-女士  -那些是我的
- Ma'am. - Those are mine.
抱歉 抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
没事 好吧 你拿着我的东西要去哪里
No--okay. Where are you going with those?
哦 好
Oh, okay.
丽塔 丽塔 怎么回事
Rita. Rita, what is going on?
突击检查
It's a raid.
我要搭个便车
♪ I'm gonna hitchhike down the road ♪
诺曼·梅勒
萨曼莎·脆饼
哦 美女 怎么
- Oh, babes? - Yeah?
帮我个忙 把这个塞进你的胸罩里
Do me a favor and stuff this in your bra.
为什么大家都这么冷静 我们被包围了哎
Why is everyone so calm? We're under siege here.
哦 没什么大不了的 这种情况一年会发生几次
Oh, it's no big deal. It happens a few times a year.
条子抢走我们的东西 道格去交罚款
The pigs grab our stuff, Doug pays a fine,
一两天内就还回来了
and they return it in a day or two.
那些流苏记得还回来 韦恩
I want those tassels back, Wayne.
我们被指控了什么
What are we being charged with?
嗷 这是美女第一次经历突击检查啊
Aw, it's baby's first raid.
你知道这次是为了什么呜
Did you hear what it's for this time?
我想可能是未成年模特
I think maybe an underage model.
我们这里还拍未成年模特吗
We shoot underage models here?
我肯定他们现在已经成年了
I'm sure they're of age now.
听着 每次他们来
Listen, every time they come in,
都有不同的理由
it's for something else.
违章区划 窝藏重犯
A zoning violation, harboring a felon.
那些指控都是在扯淡 好吗
The charges are always bullshit, okay?
这只是个由头 勒索而已
This is just a racket, a shakedown.
这是做生意最肮脏的部分
This is the dirty part of the business.
好吧 这是不是太过分了
- Oh. - Okay, is this too much?
你看起来很瘦 但有点壮
You look thin but bulgy.
我猜这些现在是给警察了
－ And I guess these are for the cops now.
我跟你说过了 皮特
We talked about this, Pete.
不许你乱动我的暖气
You don't fuck with my space heater.
不好意思了 T
- Sorry, T. - Mm-hmm.
嘿 不是说好了吗
Hey, what happened to the heads-up?
新议员 新规则
New councilwoman, new rules.
我只是个卑微的法律公仆
I'm just a humble servant of the law.
别小看自己了 老皮
Oh, don't sell yourself short, Petey.
你是个王子 我给你留个甜甜圈
You're a prince. I'll save a doughnut for you.
什么时候才能摆脱这些狗屁
When are we gonna be done with this bullshit?
等我们有飞机的时候
Around the time we get that jet.
疯了吧 他们就这么进来
This is insane-- they just come in here,
想要什么就拿什么
and they just take whatever they want.
-你怎么忍得了  -这从来没阻止过
How do you live like this? - Oh, it's never stopped us
他们办案 19次搜查了 以后还有
from getting an issue out before--19 raids and counting.
觉得这事儿值得骄傲挺怪的
That is a weird thing to be proud of.
好 周一快乐 各位
All right. Happy Monday, everybody.
好吧 看来我们在市政厅有了个新朋友
Okay, seems we got a new pal at City Hall,
而我没有给她应有的尊重
and I haven't paid her the proper respect.
36小时后印刷厂就有空闲了
So we got a spot at the printer in 36 hours.
我们得坚持住 好吗
We need to hold on to it, okay?
有人准备好标题了吗
Anybody got a title that's ready to go?
饥渴多金 你呢
"Rich & Horny," what do you got?
我存了一卷胶卷
I saved a roll of film,
3号熨斗和珍珠项链
a three-iron, and a pearl necklace.
我猜不是有趣的那种
I'm assuming not the fun kind.
-不行  -乳白辣妈
- Negative. - "Milky Moms."
他们拿走了所有东西 连娃娃都拿走了
They took everything, man, even the dolls.
-禽兽  -好
- Animals. - All right.
话说 我们不要再零敲碎打了
You know what? Let's not do this piecemeal.
所有人 把窝藏的所有东西都放在桌子上
Everybody, everything you got. Put it on the table.
你们什么毛病 我们的杂志90%是照片
What's wrong with you people? Our magazine is 90% photos.
有人窝藏了底片吗
Did anybody save any negatives?
别叫我英雄 但我裤子里藏了《风骚女子》
Well, don't call me a hero, but I got "Minx" in my pants.
里奇
Oh, Richie.
好兄弟
Good stuff.
小子 你救下样板了吗
Hey, kid. Did you, uh, save any boards?
我英勇奋战了 但是
I fought valiantly, but--
噢 天呐 不 等等
Oh, my--no, wait.
我有文章的油印本
Uh, I do have mimeographs of the articles.
你看 我
See, I, um--
唐娜飓风过后 我建立了一个备份系统
I implemented a backup system after Hurricane Donna
把我的论文散布在波基普西大街上
scattered my thesis through the streets of Poughkeepsie.
恭喜你 孩子
Well, congrats, kid,
你的出版日期推迟了一个月
your release date just got pulled up a month.
好 乔伊斯
All right, Joyce.
乔伊斯
- Joyce. - Hmm?
有你的电话
You have a call.
那不是真正的突击搜查 是勒索
It wasn't a real raid. It was a shakedown.
你知道 这是有选择性地使用当地
You know, it was selective use of local--
不 不
No, uh, no.
凯西 你知道新闻都是瞎报的
Kathy, you know the news always gets this stuff wrong.
那 请不要临阵退缩 好吗
It was--please don't get cold feet, okay?
没有你的文章《风骚女子》就不一样了
"Minx" will not be the same without your piece.
很遗憾
I'm very sorry to hear that.
我失去了所有的撰稿人
I lost every single contributor.
《堕落的儿童文学》没了
"Degendering Children's Literature," gone.
《母乳喂养的父权内涵》没了
"The Patriarchal Implications of Breastfeeding," poof.
《腋毛的美德宣言》
"A Manifesto on the Virtues of Armpit Hair."
这都是什么
Which are?
充其量也不能令人信服 我承认
Unconvincing at best. I will admit that.
但我的半本杂志都没了
But half of my magazine has just disappeared.
我明天不能去印刷厂了
I cannot go to the printer's tomorrow.
你会想到办法的
Oh, you'll figure it out.
那 你就说完了吗
Oh, that--you're done?
就这 没有其他建议了吗
That's it? There's no more advice?
听着 你从七年级就开始筹备
Well, look, you've been working on this magazine
这本杂志了 所以找些旧内容
since seventh grade, so find some old gems,
做点乔伊斯式的更新 然后 就搞定了
do a little Joyce-y update, and, wham bam, you're done.
是的 是的 我想我可以查查旧档案
Yeah, yeah, I suppose I could dip into the archives.
但我也不能把我的名字写在每一篇文章上啊
I can't put my name on every single article, though.
这不专业
That's not professional.
-那就改名  -改什么
- So change them. - What to?
诺曼·梅勒 萨曼莎·脆饼
Norman Mailer. Samantha Shortcake.
无所谓 你是编辑
It doesn't matter. You're the editor.
编辑去吧
Edit the magazine.
早晨
♪ Morning ♪
漫漫长夜辗转难眠
♪ Couldn't sleep after a long night ♪
早晨
♪ Morning ♪
我在床上打滚 穿着我的护士紧身裤
♪ I rolled around, in my nurse-wear tights ♪
布里奇特·韦斯特伯里议员
韦斯特伯里议员
Councilwoman Westbury.
你一定是雷内蒂先生吧 你十分钟前就该到了
Oh, you must be Mr. Renetti. You were due ten minutes ago.
我是不想空手而来
Well, I didn't want to show up empty-handed.
-哦  -恭喜你
- Aw. - Congratulations
以压倒性的胜利胜出
on the landslide victory.
谢谢 我不接受选民的礼物
Oh, thank you--I don't accept gifts from constituents.
还有 我会自己种花 蓝丝带园艺奖获奖者
Also, I grow my own, blue-ribbon winners--
《荆棘之冠》 连续三年
Crown of Thorns, three years running.
很好
Very nice.
那么 秘诀是什么呢
Well, what's the secret?
-爱  -那太好了
- Love. - Oh, that's nice.
你介意拿一下另一个棕色的文件夹吗
Would you mind grabbing that other brown file up there?
-对我来说有点高了  -我很乐意
It's a little high for me. - It'd be my pleasure.
我猜你是为了今早
So I'm assuming that you're here about the raid
对你场所的突击检查来的
conducted on your premises this morning?
是的
Yeah.
传讯清单很有创意
The list of citations was very creative.
通风不当
Improper ventilation, um,
过期的暗室材料
expired darkroom materials,
我最喜欢的是啥来着
and, uh, what was my favorite?
出口通道 这到底是什么意思
Access to egress. What does that even mean?
安全是第一位的
Well, safety is job number one.
是的 我完全同意
Yeah, I agree, absolutely.
你看 之前
You see, in the past,
当然 在我交了罚款之后
uh, after I paid my fines, of course,
我能够通过向议员选择的
I've been able to expedite the release of my materials
慈善机构捐款
by making a personal donation
来加速我资料的归还
to the charity of the councilman's choice.
所以
- Ah. - So...
我的一些前任确实都是
Wow, yes, some of my predecessors
丰富多彩的人物
were colorful characters.
我上班第一天在桌子里发现了一把枪
I found a gun in my desk on my first day.
我据为己有了
I kept it.
那就给全国步枪协会捐款吧
Well, maybe a donation to the NRA, then?
雷内蒂先生 你知不知道在山谷
Oh, Mr. Renetti, are you aware that in the Valley,
色情作家比儿科医生还多
there are more pornographers than there are pediatricians?
我不知道
I was not aware.
但如果你需要医生 我有个表亲叫
But if you need a doctor, I got a cousin named--
-不必了  -好滴
- That won't be necessary. - Okay.
你知道 我当选是为了恢复
You know, I was elected to restore
这个社区的价值观 所以
the values of this community, so, you know,
这意味着要把杂草连根拔起
that's gonna mean pulling the weeds up by the roots.
那些剥削年轻女孩
Companies that exploit young girls
压低房地产价值
and drive down property values
让好男人在信仰上受挫的公司
and lead good men to stumble in their faith.
十二污人
The Dirty Dozen--
盛年书店 浪漫沙龙
Adulty's Bookstore, Romantix Saloon,
挑逗角
The Tickle Corner.
你 你到底想干什么
What are you--what are you trying to do here,
挖出山谷的心脏吗
cut out the Valley's heart?
或者说是肿瘤
Or its tumor.
嗯 议员
Well, Councilwoman,
这些生意都不违法
there's nothing illegal about any of these businesses.
不管你觉得它们有多不合你口味
Despite how distasteful you might find them,
这仍然是一个自由的国家
this is still a free country.
政府的工作是
The job of government
保护公民不受劣质演员侵害
is to protect its citizens from bad actors.
如果那些演员觉得我的监督太麻烦
If those actors find my oversight too onerous,
他们可以去其他地方另起炉灶
they are free to set up shop elsewhere.
我听说奥克斯纳德很不错 就在水边
I heard Oxnard is lovely, and it's by the water.
别这样
Come on.
如果你不介意的话 我要和
So if you'll excuse me, I have a tea
美国革命女儿协会喝杯茶去
with the Daughters of the American Revolution.
相信我 你不会想让她们久等的
And trust me, you don't want to keep those gals waiting.
我就不送你了
You can see yourself out.
-烦死了  -闭嘴
- This sucks. - Zip it.
嘿 美女
♪ Hey, mama ♪
看起来不错
♪ Showing up lookin good ♪
她们细腿翘着
♪ With them skinny legs twisting around ♪
穿着热裤
♪ In them hot pants ♪
你看 饶了我吧
♪ Look at that, have mercy ♪
乔伊斯姨妈 我从来没见过
Auntie Joyce, I've never seen--
嘿 我在车里怎么跟你说的
Hey, what did I tell you in the car?
低头 嘴巴闭上
Eyes down, mouth shut.
汤米 我没想到会在这里见到你
Tommy, I was not expecting to see you here.
我也没想到有人会把
And I was not expecting someone
他同学的屁股点着了
to light his classmate's buttocks on fire.
不是他的屁股 是他的屁
It wasn't his butt. It was his fart.
尤金现在在烧伤病房 托马斯
Eugene is in the burn ward, Thomas.
我现在都不想看你
I can't even look at you right now.
剩下的箱子 快点
Rest of the boxes, chop-chop.
天呐 乔伊斯 这地方还挺热闹了
My God, Joycie, this place is quite an operation.
相信我 都是用胶带粘在一起的
Well, trust me, it's held together with masking tape.
你读过这篇文章吗
Aw, you ever read this article?
《浴血奋战：为月经认知而战》
"Out for Blood: The Fight for Menstrual Reckoning."
当然了 它挑战了我对经期的
Oh, of course, it challenged everything
所有认知
I thought I knew about menstrual reckonings.
-好的  -哦 这提醒我了
- Okay. - Oh, that reminds me.
我得去拿番茄酱 今天周一吃烘肉卷
I got to pick up ketchup. It's meatloaf Monday.
-耶 雪莉来喽  -嗨
- Yay, Shelly's here! - Hi.
你想转转吗 我可以带你啊
Do you want a tour? It's kind of my thing.
是啊 我什么都想看看
Yeah, I want to see everything.
等等 我是不是
Wait, do I, or--
是 确实 最好别去那个角落
Yes, you do. Maybe not that corner.
哦 这可太有趣了
Oh, that's so much fun.
但是 嗯 转转这事你能不能稍等一会
But, um, could you just wait on that,
跟我看一遍这些箱子
and instead, could you just help me go through these boxes
来挑出最好的 最好的文章
and pick out the best-- you know, the best articles?
-哦  -好的
- Oh. - Okay.
我是说 我大概能在这待一小时
I mean, I guess I could be here for an hour.
哦 那太好了
Oh, great.
我该让这淘气包去哪
Where should I park this little pyro?
-嗯 那个大厅不错  -跟着我 小可爱
- Um, the lobby should be fine. - Follow me, cutie.
哦 啊 你得明白 你在这看到的任何一个女人
Oh, uh, just know that any of the women you see here
都是自愿被我们拍照的
appear in our photos voluntarily
并且都被给予了恰当的酬劳 好吗
and are appropriately compensated, okay?
哦 但你也别期望跟你调情的
Oh, but you should also not expect the girls
女孩能有多么性开放
that you're romantic with to be as open with their sexuality.
因为 哦 如果她们确实这样了
'Cause--oh, but if they are--
-乔伊斯 -怎么
- Joyce. - Yeah.
-他才13  -哦 好吧
- He's 13. - Oh, okay.
你为什么把童子军肩带拿回来了
You took scout sashes, why?
不知道 可能是它是离门最近的东西吧
Don't know it was the closest thing to the door.
就是你拿了我的东西 我也得拿你的
You know what? You take my stuff, I'm taking yours.
这是我听到过的最蠢的事了
That's the dumbest shit I've ever heard.
-我们有麻烦了  -我知道
- We got a real problem here. - I know.
我看向那女人眼睛的时候 我就知道她想了结我们
I looked in that woman's eyes. She wants to end us.
听着 我们得把这些板子拿回去
Look, we got to get those boards back,
给她看看在这地界我们也是有朋友的
show her that we got friends in this community, too.
那我们怎么做呢
And how are we supposed to do that?
我不知道 乞讨 借 还是偷
I don't know. Beg, borrow, or steal.
她以为她掌控山谷吗 不 我才是
She thinks she's the Valley. Mm-mm, I'm the Valley.
好的 等等 卡蓬
Okay, slow down, Capone.
卡篷是美国黑手党老大
等我们到了一无所有的地步
It was one thing to do that stuff
才是这么做的时候
back in the day when we had nothing to lose.
我们现在有些实际资产需要保全
Got real assets to protect now.
得守规矩
Got to follow some rules.
是啊 但这不是我拍成人片的原因
Yeah, not exactly why I got into porn.
我可以联系一些人 看看是谁给她吹的风
I can call some people, find out who's got her ear,
你知道 这是光明正大的政治手段
you know, aboveboard political stuff.
放长线 钓大鱼
Play the long game.
把底洗干净 变得强大到她不再敢惹我们
Come out clean, get so big she can't fuck with us anymore.
是 也许你是对的
Yeah, maybe you're right.
那让我们试试你的方法
Let's try it your way.
好嘞
All right.
嗯 好了 哪些是你们最喜欢的
Uh, okay, so, um, which ones were your favorites?
都是
All of them.
各位 没事的
Guys, it's okay.
我又不是逮着一个不放 对吗
I'm not married to anything, all right?
尽管我确实喜欢
Although I am a little in love
那篇婚内强暴的文章
with that article on marital rape.
哦 对 那篇真棒
Oh, yeah. That one was neat.
你觉得婚内强暴很棒吗
You think marital rape is neat?
你没读过它 是吧
You didn't read it. Okay.
嗯 我们真的很努力了
Uh, we tried really hard.
只是能理解的部分不多
There just wasn't much to latch on to.
-没错  -好吧 好吧
- Yeah. - All right, all right.
嗯 雪莉 你一定喜欢那篇 家政学
Uh, Shelly, you must have liked "Home Economics:
《家庭补偿之窘境》
The Contretemps on Domestic Expiation"?
乔伊斯 抱歉 我根本没法把它读完
I'm so sorry, Joycie. I couldn't get through it.
但我就是为你写的那篇啊
But I literally wrote it for you.
它论证了妻子
It debates whether wives
是否应该为做家务得到补偿
should be compensated for their housework.
那我怎么知道啊
How was I supposed to know that?
《家庭补偿之窘境》
"The Contretemps on Domestic Expiation."
我觉得我说的已经够清楚了
I don't know how I could be any clearer.
其实 假如你把名字改为
Well, uh, what if you called it
《孩子拿钱做家务 那妈妈呢》
"Kids Get Paid For Chores Shouldn't Moms?"
-这个好  -我肯定会去读这个
- Mm. - I would read that.
好吧 如果我们只想吸引那些低端读者的话
Well, yeah, if we want to go for the low-hanging fruit.
对我来说 这可能更像是个能量问题
For me, it was more, like, an energy thing.
这些文章好像不喜欢被读
It's like the articles didn't want to be read.
哦 天啊 你这句话说的真棒
Oh, my gosh. You put that so well.
好像哪怕我试图去读都会惹他们生气
It's like they were angry at me for even trying.
乔伊斯 就这一段 我都感觉在被攻击
Joyce, this is one paragraph. I feel attacked.
-对啊  -好吧
- Yeah. - All right, okay.
看来窗户纸都捅破了 那继续 我能承受
I guess the gloves are off. Go ahead, I can take it.
-易怒  -毫无生气
- Crabby. - Lifeless.
卖弄学问
Pedantic.
是的 我查了 这些词我都查了
Yeah, I looked it up. I looked all these up.
我觉得我还不如直接读字典呢
I guess I mostly read the dictionary.
好的 那么 谢谢你们的建议
All right, well, um, thank you for your suggestions.
我一定会好好考虑一下的
I will definitely give them some thought.
-哦  -啊 乔
- Oh. - Uh, Jo--
哦 抱歉 明白了
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that. Understood.
不 谢谢你
No, thank you.
好的
Okay.
你老看我是找我有事吗
Can I help you with something?
哦 我就是陪我妈来的
Oh, I'm just here with my mother.
她是拍《饥渴主妇》还是《乳白辣妈》
She a Horny Housewife or Milky Mom?
我希望都不是 我姨妈是这的一个编辑
Neither, I hope. Um, my aunt is an editor here.
而我被暑期班开除了
And I got kicked out of summer school.
哦 我曾经也是
Oh, been there.
我惹了不少麻烦
I'm in a lot of trouble.
那么 我们看看怎么才能让你找点乐子
Well, let's see if we can brighten your day.
哦 我爱你宝贝
♪ Well, I love you, baby ♪
我就在这告诉你
♪ I'm telling you right here ♪
但请别让我在你和一瓶啤酒之间
♪ But please don't make me decide, baby ♪
进行抉择 宝贝
♪ Between you and a bottle of beer ♪
宝贝 来我身边
♪ Baby, come on over ♪
来我身边 来啊 宝贝
♪ Come on over to my side, come on, baby ♪
我身边
♪ My side ♪
哦 我可能活不过21
♪ Well, I may not live past 21 ♪
但这么死去又何妨
♪ But, whoo, what a way to die ♪
你的爱飘忽不定 宝贝
♪ Your lovin'fluctuates, baby ♪
这谁都知道
♪ And everybody knows ♪
但是一瓶冰镇斯特罗啤酒的温度
♪ But the temperature always stays the same ♪
永远不变
♪ On an ice-cold bottle of Stroh's ♪
所以 宝贝 快过来吧
♪ So, baby, come on over ♪
哦 来到我身边
♪ Oh, come on over to my side ♪
来吧 宝贝
♪ Come on over, honey ♪
我可能活不过21
♪ Well, I may not live past 21 ♪
但这么死去又何妨
♪ But, whoo, what a way... ♪
哦 她在那呢
Oh, there she is,
山谷资格最老的未婚女子
the Valley's most eligible bachelorette.
只有一个真诚的男人
It's going to take an honest man
才能让我成为一个真诚的女人 小道格
to make an honest woman out of me, Dougie.
而这条就把你淘汰了
That rules you out.
这事没有先例啊
This never happened.
我都不知道你在说什么
I don't even know what you're talking about.
我进去一趟很快就出来
I will be in and out in no time.
谢谢了
Thank you.
埃尔森·柯林斯房产
哦 来我身边吧 来吧
♪ Oh, come on over to my side, come on ♪
谢谢您的提交
我们抱歉地通知您
我可能活不过21
♪ Well, I may not live past 21 ♪
不适合商业发行
不够吸引眼球
枯燥无味
但这么死去又何妨
♪ But, whoo, what a way to die ♪
怒气火上浇油
过于紧张
它很臭
雷内蒂先生 在我们今天见面之后
Mr. Renetti, after our little meeting today,
我打听了一下你
I asked around about you.
哦 你还真不是个善茬啊
Ooh, you are quite the rapscallion.
女士
Okay, listen, lady,
我的雇员们也是你的选民啊
my employees are your constituents, too.
如果我的公司没了他们要怎么办
What happens to them if I lose my business?
我发现谷里的人承压能力特别强
Well, I've found Valley folk to be tremendously resilient.
按照现在经济发展的态势
And with the dynamic economy that we're building,
未来会有很多
there's gonna be plenty of opportunity
合适的工作机会给他们的
for people to pursue respectable work.
你们什么时候进行重新选举
When are you up for reelection?
放心吧 重选之前
I'm certain I will have your vote
你一定会投我一票的
before that day arrives.
顺便说一句 我办公室里有个袋子
By the way, there was a bag in my office.
你去办公室之后
It grew feet and scurried off
它突然长了脚自己就跑了
right about the time you popped by.
童子军17队今晚要拍照
Troop 17 has their pictures tonight,
姑娘们要是没有肩带就没法摆姿势了
and the girls cannot pose without their sashes.
真不幸
That is so unfortunate.
看来我们俩都需要拿回自己的东西 是不是
Well, it seems like we both need something back, don't we?
-你收着吧 卡萝尔  -她不允许啊
- Keep'em, Carole. - She won't let me.
-嗨  -嗨 乔伊斯 你还好吧
- Hi. - Hi, Joyce, you okay?
角落里一共有32条长毛围巾
There were 32 different boas stuffed in the corner,
所以我把它们按照颜色
so I have organized them now
长度还有毛的种类分开了
into color, length, and species.
看上去好多了
- Oh. - Oh, looks a lot better.
是啊
- Mm-hmm. - It does, mm-hmm.
嘿 亲爱的
Hey, babes.
我们在想哈
So we were thinking, you know,
我们一直在批评你的杂志
maybe it wasn't very helpful of us
但是又没有什么自己的想法
to criticize your magazine
感觉这样都没出到力
and not have any ideas of our own.
所以我们想了个主意
So we came up with some stuff. - Oh.
既然我们需要内容来填充更多页面
Since we need to fill more pages,
我调整了一些现有材料的布局
I tweaked the layout of some of the existing material.
根据节育文章
I created a jazzy infographic
画了一个有趣的信息图
based on the birth-control article.
一整页
I added a whole page.
然后我把标题
And I changed the headline
从《艾森施塔特对贝尔德：赋予生殖正义》
from "Eisenstadt v. Baird: Reproductive Justice Granted"
改成了《万岁 现在单身女孩可以吃药了》
to "Hooray, Now Single Gals Can Get the Pill."
看见没 特别吸引人吧
See? It's catchy.
这变化还不小哈
Hmm. That, uh--that is a change.
最后不能不提一下
And last but hopefully not least,
我用了杂志插页中
I used the reject Polaroids
作废的宝丽来照片制作了这个
from the centerfold casting and made this.
-我要看的是啥  -是个连连看啊
- What am I looking at? - It's a game.
把人和对应的丁丁连在一起
You match the man with the penis.
连连看：它是谁的丁丁
太可爱了
It's cute.
-为什么  -首先
- Why? - Well, first of all,
这比你想的可难多了 不信你试试
it's a lot tougher than you think--I mean, try it.
我们认为从你那篇
Yeah, and we thought it might be a little bit shocking
关手切割女性生殖器的文章
to flip from your article on female genital mutilation
直接跳到消防员的那两页上可能会让人有点不适应
straight into a two-page spread of that fireman's dingle dong.
所以觉得你 你可能需要一个过渡页
Yeah, you-you need a transition, kind of, like,
就像两道菜中间加勺冰淇淋
a scoop of sorbet in between courses.
-对  -真好
- Yeah. - That's good.
所以你们一整天就干了这事吗
So this is what you've been working on all day?
-雪莉还弄了头发  -是的
- And Shelly's hair. - Yes.
-我还化了妆  -她看上去特别美吧
- And my makeup. - Doesn't she look gorgeous?
-别说我了  -我真不知道要怎么办
- Stop it. - I don't know how to do this.
我不知道怎么才能让你们理解
I don't know how to make you understand
这个杂志不是开玩笑的
that this magazine is not a joke.
我们不会搞什么卡通字体
You know, we don't do bubble letters
或者通俗易懂的标题什么
or dumbed-down headlines
也不能加入没有任何社会价值的丁丁游戏
or penis games with no redeeming social value.
天哪 道格让我做的事
My God, Doug is making me
简直就是不可能完成的任务
do something that is impossible here,
他还一点支持都不给我
and he is giving me absolutely no support.
乔伊斯 我 我们就是来支持你的啊 我们可以帮你的
Joycie, w-we're your support. We're trying to help.
是 但你们却一点忙都帮不上
Yeah, but you can't,
因为一本真正的杂志需要的是真正的撰稿人和编辑
because a real magazine has real writers and real editors,
不像星期一烘肉卷那样
and it's not cobbled together
最后一分钟随便拼凑一下就能成的
at the last minute like it's Meatloaf Monday.
你说的对 是我们不知所云了
You're right. I don't know what we were thinking.
祝你好运 乔伊斯
Good luck, Joyce.
我以前从没见过这么大个的
Wow, I've never seen one this big before.
汤米 你手上的活太好了
Tommy, you're so good with your hands.
天 你们搞什么呢
Wow. What is going on in here?
不行 小先生
No, sir.
没什么啊 他只是在给我们讲跟尤金的事呢
No, uh, he just told us about what happened with Eugene.
-是啊  -太倒霉了
- Yeah. - Tough break.
-太惨了  -真悲催
- It's so sad. - Just awful.
孩子总是会犯错的嘛
You know, kids make mistakes.
快点好起来 尤金
谢谢你们
thank you.
客气了
Sure.
-好了 走吧  -真好
- Okay, let's go. - So good.
-失陪了  -好
- Excuse me. - Okay.
再见 妮基 杰德 罗拉 安布尔 罗克西 彻丽
Bye, Nikki, Jade, Lola, Amber, Roxy, Cherry.
-再见 汤米  -再见
Bye, Tommy. - Bye.
开什么玩笑
You got to be kidding me.
韦斯特伯里离开她家了
Okay, Westbury comes out of her house, you know.
你的车要跟上
Obviously there's your car.
今天晚点又要去吃午餐 也许是安东尼奥餐吧
Later in the day, fancy lunch, Antonio's maybe?
你的车又要跟上
There's your car again.
我们什么时候去她家
When do we go in her house?
我们不能擅自闯入她家 我们只是恐吓她
－ We're not breaking in. This is intimidation.
只要能让她知道这一点就行
We're just trying to get in her head.
简单点不行吗 把她直接弄死
It would be easier, though, just to kill her.
阿尔卡迪 拜托 这是个简单的计划 不要即兴发挥
Arkady, please, this is a simple plan, no improvising.
我们只要恐吓她就行
We're just trying to intimidate her--
什么鬼 失陪一下
Oh, what the fuck? Excuse me, gentlemen.
-乔伊斯  -嗨
Joyce. - Hi.
如果你完成的早然后想来这
If you finished early and you're coming in here
喝一杯 那我可真是想错你了
to tie one on, boy, have I misjudged you.
-我不可能完成  -你当然可以
- No, I-I can't finish. - Of course you can finish.
做领导就是这样的 你可以搞定
Okay, this is what it means to be a boss--you're just fine.
也许我就不是做领导的料
－ Well, maybe I'm not cut out
因为我
for leadership because I'm not getting...
-他们俩是谁  -合伙人
Who are those guys? - Ah, they're associates.
没什么好担心的
Nothing to worry about.
他们为什么盯着我
Why are they staring at me, then?
我不知道 只是好奇吧
I don't know. They're curious gentlemen.
你刚才说什么 你需要什么
What were you saying? What do you need?
你不是又在密谋什么吧
Are you plotting something?
没有 我没有密谋
No, I'm not plotting anything.
乔伊斯 你负责编辑 我负责业务的事 好吗
Joyce, you handle editorial. I'll handle the business, okay?
-这是业务吗  -对啊
- This is business? - Yes, this is business.
我对付这些政客都15年了
I've been dealing with politicians for 15 years.
他们来了一茬又走 只有我还在
They come, and they go. I'm still here.
没错 坦率的说 简直就是奇迹
Yeah, which is a miracle, frankly.
你是又打算绑架童子军呢
What, are you gonna kidnap some scouts
还是偷走他们的曲奇
or steal their cookies?
你听说了
So you heard about that?
-对  -好吧 我不偷东西的 乔伊斯
- Yes. - Look, I don't steal, Joyce...
也许那些人就不值得拥有
From people who don't deserve it, okay?
我想做点实事
What I'm trying to do is real,
很不容易 而且没有捷径
and it's hard, and there are no shortcuts.
我看明白了 我求助是来错地方了
I can see I came to the wrong place for any help.
够了
That's enough, okay?
这样吧
How about this?
你他妈干好你的活 我也干好我的
Do your fucking job, and I'll do mine.
行吧 走着瞧
Okay, we'll see about that.
-没事  -很好
- We're good, gentlemen. - Spasibo.
我的斯维特拉娜会喜欢这些的
My Svetlana will love these.
请吧
Pozhaluysta.
好了 姑娘们 注意了
Okay, girls. Your attention, please.
我知道这不是真的 但如果说要做童子军
I know these aren't real, but if there's one thing
需要做到的就是即兴表演和保持素养
scouts know how to do, it's improvise and stay chaste.
韦斯特伯里议员
Councilwoman Westbury.
你好 我是乔伊斯·普里格
Hello. Hi, I am Joyce Prigger.
自从您65年成为校董
I am a big admirer of yours,
我就是您的粉丝
ever since you ran for school board in '65.
我不能坐在那看着他们
Oh, well, I couldn't just sit back and watch them
教我们的孩子塞林格是不是
teach our kids Salinger, now, could I?
绝对不行
Certainly not, no.
但是你 你一直是个榜样
Um, but you, you're an inspiration--
因为你可以很好的平衡
the way you've been able
家庭和事业
to balance raising a family with a career.
南加利福尼亚州的
I mean, the first city councilwoman
第一任女议员
in all of Southern California.
你简直就是先锋啊
You're a pioneer.
那还不是因为我有
Oh, well, I have a bottomless can
永不枯竭的福杰仕咖啡和能干的女员工们
of Folgers and a crackerjack all-female staff.
你是有意从政吗
Are you looking to get into politics?
不是 我只是 我来这是
Oh, uh, no, um, no, I'm just--I'm actually here
还这些的
to, um, return these
同时替道格·雷内蒂道歉
with apologies from Doug Renetti.
看来你们俩一开始相处的不是很融洽
Okay, well, it seems like you two got off on the wrong foot.
玛丽安 做个好人 把这些发下去
Mm-hmm. Marian, be a lamb and, um, distribute these
然后组织一下姑娘们
and, uh, organize the girls.
是 女土
Ja, fraulein.
替我女儿道歉哈
Apologies for my daughter.
为她那怪异的幽默感
She has a unique sense of humor.
没事
Yeah.
我觉得你可能误会了底袋钱
Um, I think you got the wrong impression of Bottom Dollar,
还有道格·雷内蒂先生 因为
and even of Doug Renetti, actually, because,
我知道他有时候脾气不太好
look, I know he can be a little rough around the edges,
但是
but you know what?
只有他肯给我机会
He was the only one who would take a chance
出版我的杂志
on publishing my magazine.
这是给新一代女性的指南
It's a road map for the next generation of women,
给像你女儿这样的姑娘们重新定义未来的杂志
for girls like yours who will redefine what's possible.
是嘛
Really?
你的杂志中都有什么文章呢
What kind of articles are in this magazine of yours?
非常重要的题目 比如
Oh, well, important topics, you know--
教育法第九修正案 新时代等等
uh, Title IX, ERA.
安娜贝拉
Mm, mm-hmm. Annabelle!
对于新时代你有什么想法
What do you think of the ERA?
我不想被征召入伍然后死在越南
I don't want to get drafted and die in Vietnam.
朱莉 你觉得呢
Julie, would you like to weigh in?
如果我离婚了
If I get divorced,
一分钱都不会给我丈夫
I don't want to pay my husband alimony.
即便他抚养孩子
Even if he raises the kids
而你去上医科学校也不给他钱吗
while you attend medical school?
好吧 那加入男童子军的
All right, well, what about the right
权力呢
to join a male scout group
如果你想学习木雕
if you want to learn about wood carving
还有野外生存 而不是
and wilderness survival, instead of--
你刻了很多木头吗
Do you carve a lot of wood?
没有 但我认为我应该有权利去这么做
No, but I do believe that I should have the right to.
-这个有翻领  -我 我不知道
- This one has a turtleneck. - I just--I don't know.
这可比看上去要难的多了
It's a lot harder than it looks.
天哪
Oh, my God.
-答案在哪呢  -给我
- Where's the answer key? - Give that to me!
我滴个神啊
Oh, my gosh. - Oh, it--
这就是你的指南吗
Is this your road map?
这指南是指向地狱的吗
I'm fairly certain that leads straight to hell.
不用这么大惊小怪的吧 不过就是丁丁而已
Oh, for Pete's sake, they're just penises,
你就别管了 虽然有点傻 但挺搞笑的
minding their own business-- it's silly, and it's fun.
这就是我说的
And there's something to be said
别太把自己当回事了哈
for not taking oneself so seriously.
很明显 我们对于
Ah, well, we clearly have very different ideas
如何塑造未来女性的思维这事上有分歧
about how to shape the minds of young women.
如果你已经打算
And if you've already aligned yourself
跟雷内蒂这种人混在一块 那我向你保证
with the likes of Mr. Renetti, I can assure you that your days
你在圣费尔南多谷的日子已经屈指可数了
in the San Fernando Valley are numbered.
好了 姑娘们 别只顾着逗乐子了
Okay, girls, enough monkey business.
站好队 不要慢吞吞的 走吧
Form up! Don't dawdle. Let's go.
大家要面带笑容挺直脊梁
Now, I want big smiles, straight spines,
缩回肚子
and flat tummies.
吸回去 露丝
Suck it in, Ruth.
幸好你们都还在
Oh, thank God you're still here.
好吧 我们还要做杂志呢
Okay. We have a magazine to make.
我们吗
Oh, we?
今天的事我太抱歉了
Look I am so, so sorry about today, okay?
你们今天充满热情和想法
You came in with enthusiasm and ideas,
可我却完全没有当做一回事
and I just stole your joie de vivre.
事实是 我脑子里装了太多事了
The truth is, I am in way over my head
我必须得想清楚
but I have to figure it out.
是我们必须得想清楚
We have to figure it out,
就算不是为了我 为了下一代女性
if not for us, then for the girls who come next,
因为我看到了未来 实在是太吓人了
because I have seen the future, and it is terrifying.
比你下午4点的样子还吓人吗
Like you at 4:00 p.m.?
哦 比那惊心动魄多了
Oh, scarier.
-我们开工吧老大  -好
- Let's get to work, boss. - Oh, okay.
哎呀
Oh, my God.
我记得
♪ I remember ♪
第一次相遇的时候说过我们永不分离
♪ when we first met we said we'd never part ♪
我们永不分离
♪ We'd never part ♪
亲爱的 我们都明白
♪ Darling, we both understood that ♪
你的一切都如此美好
♪ Everything was good about you ♪
没有你我根本活不下去
♪ I can't live without you ♪
现在我们分了手 亲爱的
♪ Now that we are broken up, darling ♪
我的生活不能没有你
♪ My life is nothing without you ♪
我们
♪ We... ♪
-这个布局够简单不  -里奇
- This layout, was it Curt? - Richie.
不只是摄影 他简直是天生就有设计的眼光
It's not just photography. He has a real eye for design.
太好了 这个游戏是新的
Great. The game is new.
有意思吧 斑比挺逗的
It's fun. Bambi's fun.
她喜欢混搭
She loves her mix and match.
我不知道你怎么做到的
Look, I don't know how you did it,
但我觉得这是我看到的最好的一版
but this is the best version of this rag I've seen so far.
是吧
Right?
是啊 终于弄成了
Yeah, it really came together.
甚至还有萨曼莎·脆饼呢
Ah, even Samantha Shortcake got a piece in it.
萨曼莎·肖特是个化名
Samantha Short is a nom de plume
我可以尽情使用
I will use very proudly.
非常好 真不错
Great, good stuff.
道格 其实你是个好老板
You know, Doug, in your own way...
不过跟别人不太一样而已
you're actually a really good boss.
我 我想说谢谢你 给了《风骚女子》一个机会
I just--I want to say thank you for giving "Minx" a chance.
你不是想上我吧 普里格
Are you trying to get in my pants, Prigger?
因为我现在可不在办公室里搞了
Cause I don't put out in the office anymore.
好吧
Okay.
我可是接受教训了
I learned that lesson many times.
对了 我喜欢你的新标题
Oh, by the way, I love the new headlines.
感觉又有力度又容易理解
They're punchy and understandable,
我没想到你能做到这一点
which I didn't know you could be.
干得好
Good work.
汤米
Tommy!
-是鲍比  -是吗
- It was Bobby. - Yeah, was it?
那可是我祖母的猫头鹰
That was my grandmother's owl!
小点声
Turn it down!
汉德森家自己有电视
Okay, the Hendersons have their own TV.
他们可不用听我们的节目
They don't want to hear ours.
真是够够的了
Jesus Christ!
你知道为什么孩子一生下来就像爸爸吗
Do you know why babies come out looking like the dad?
这就是进化论的结果
It's some, like, evolutionary thing,
这样男人才不会把自己的宝宝给吃了
so men won't eat their young.
但生物学对女人有什么帮助 乔伊斯
But was does biology do for the moms, Joyce?
我有个疯狂的想法
I have kind of a crazy idea.
我已经试过安眠酮了
Oh, no. I already tried Quaaludes.
你来为《风骚女子》工作好不好
No, what if you came to work for "Minx"?
每天上午或者一周只工作几天
I mean, mornings or a few times a week,
你看怎么合适怎么来
whatever's good for you.
怎么了 因为昨天事情很顺利吗
－ What, because yesterday went so well?
我知道自己状态也不好
Okay. I know I was not at my best.
有时候人们不像你一样做事
You know, just because people can't do what you do
并不等于他们就不会做事
doesn't mean they can't do something.
看见没 这就是我想说的
See, yeah, that right there, that's what I need.
你和斑比 蒂娜还有里奇相处的很好
You're so good with Bambi and Tina and Richie.
而且你 你还总是比我有趣
It's--and you've always been funnier than me.
-降低标准  -好吧 谢谢
- Low bar. - Okay, thank you.
其实仔细一想
I mean, when you think about it,
做杂志和做肉卷
making a magazine isn't entirely different
其实也不是完全不一样
from making a meatloaf.
额滴神哪 汤半
Oh, my God. Jesus, Tommy!
不 是鲍比
Oh, no, that's Bobby.
他的肛门要蓝一些
His anus is bluer.
好吧 你真的需要离开家去工作才行
Okay, you really, really need to get out of your house.
嘿
Hey, Barb.
给我一杯波本再加杯代基里酒
Yeah, give me a Maker's and a banana daiquiri.
-没问题 亲爱的  -谢了
- Sure thing, baby cakes. - Thanks.
你看《风骚女子》了吗
You seen "Minx"?
很不错啊 虽然经历坎坷
Looks good, bumpy ride.
是啊 那丫头居然弄成了 不错
Yeah, kid pulled it off. It's great.
勉强吧 但是给我们争取到了24到36小时
Barely. But bought us 24 to 36 hours.
看来我们要到明年
Well, it looks like we won't be getting that jet
才能弄到那架飞机了
until next year, huh?
没错 我们这个女议员也有不为人知的
Yep, seems our new councilwoman has a few secrets
秘密呢
of her own.
我们给她看这个的话
I mean, we show her this,
她会立刻转向其他人了吧
she moves on to someone else right away.
真行
Man...
你怎么弄到的
How'd you get this?
别人久我个人情 我让对方还了
I had a favor to call in, and I used it.
你知道这个就行了
That's all you need to know.
太好了
Great.
放到我拿不到的地方去吧
Put that somewhere where I can't get it.
给你 亲爱的
Here you go, hon.
帮我个忙
Hey, do me a favor.
按兵不动 这样才能成事
Stay straight. That's how this works.
一 二
One, two.
心满意足
♪ Satisfaction ♪
我只想心满意足
♪ Satisfaction is what I want ♪
心满意足
♪ Satisfaction ♪
我只想心满意足
♪ Satisfaction is what I ♪
我已经厌倦了被爱抛弃
♪ I'm tired of being the one that love passes by ♪
我想心满意足
♪ I want to be satisfied - Oh, yeah ♪
我什么都敢尝试
♪ There's nothing I won't try ♪
只要你给我个机会
♪ If I could get a chance ♪
我就可以拥有罗曼史
♪ Then I would have romance, if I had it once ♪
因为我只想
♪ 'Cause satisfaction is what I want ♪
心满意足
♪ Satisfaction ♪
♪ Oh, yeah - Satisfaction ♪
就是我想要的
♪ Oh, yeah, is what I want ♪
爱会流逝
♪ Love is passing ♪
心满意足
♪ Satisfaction ♪
没人给你 我要怎么做
♪ No one gives you, what did I do? ♪
我什么都不做
♪ I didn't do nothing ♪
不值得那日复一日
♪ Don't deserve the sun coming in ♪
只要给我个机会
♪ If I could get one chance ♪
耶
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
证明我值得
♪ To prove that I'm worthy, to be qualified ♪
如果给我个机会让我拥有爱
♪ To have love desired, if I had a chance ♪
我只想心满意足
♪ Satisfaction is what I want ♪
-我只希望  -有你的陪伴
♪ I'm just hopin' - For your company ♪
-如果我坚持  -我就能得到满足
♪ If I hold on - It will surely come... ♪